<?xml version= "1.0"?>

<levels>
	<level>
		<title>Level 1</title>
		<part> 
			<title>Part 1</title>
			<exercices>
				<ex>
					<hint>Left Hand</hint>
					<text>ffff dddd ssss aaaa ffff dddd ssss aaaa ffff dddd ssss aaaa</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Left Hand</hint>
					<text>asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf asdf</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Left Hand</hint>
					<text>fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa fdsa</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Right Hand</hint>
					<text>jjjj kkkk llll ;;;; jjjj kkkk llll ;;;; jjjj kkkk llll ;;;;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Right Hand</hint>
					<text>jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl; jkl;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Right Hand</hint>
					<text>;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj ;lkj</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>fd fds fdsa jk jkl jkl; fd fds fdsa jk jkl jkl; fd fds fdsa jk jkl jkl;</text>
				</ex>
			</exercices>
		</part>
		<part> 
			<title>Part 2</title>
			<exercices>
				<ex>
					<hint>Left Hand</hint>
					<text>deed frrf deer reed red deed frrf deer reed red deed frrf deer reed red</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Left Hand</hint>
					<text>free freed fred feed fed free freed fred feed fed free freed fred feed fed</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<hint>Left Hand</hint>
					<text>reef reef ref ref refer refer defer defer referred deferred refereed</text>
				</ex>	
				<ex>
					<hint>Right Hand</hint>
					<text>juuj kiik juj kik juuj kiik juj kik juuj kiik juj kik juuj kiik juj kik</text>
				</ex>			
				<ex>
					<text>jude jude dud dud dude dude rude rude due due rudder rudder</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>fur fur fir fir fire fire fired fired ride ride fried fried rider rider</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>kid kid did did die die died died dried dried ride ride drier drier</text>
				</ex>			
				<ex>
					<text>red deer; feed freddie; red fire; free feed; fried deer;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>eddie died; free ride; eddie fired fred; did eddie die;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>edifier rider dude freed red fur deer; kidder eddie rudder fed red deer;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>freed fed red deer died; fred fuji fried freed fed red deer;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>duke jeered rude referee jed; did irked kirk fire rude jerk;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>did freddie duke feed jeff kirk free fried red deer; rude eddie kerr jerked duke kirk;</text>
				</ex>
			</exercices>
		</part>
	</level>
	
	<level>
		<title>Level 2</title>
		<part>
			<title>Part 1</title>
			<exercices>
				<ex>
					<text>gh gh gh gh gh gh gh gh gh gh gh gh gh</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>th th th th th th th th ght ght ght ght ght ght ght</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>feet fret get greet regret regretted rift drift gift gifted fig figure</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>dirt diet tire tired retire retired tried he her here the there</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>jut jutted jud jug judge judged hug hugged dug drug drugged</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>ugh high higher thigh tight fight right fright tight height eighth hut hurt</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>freddie tried the fridge; the right fridge; keith agreed; the huge free feed;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>red jug; guide the tight red kite higher; the hired guide urged the rugged hiker;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>the right judge; the third huge tiger tried; true ruth tried the third free gift;</text>
				</ex>
			</exercices>
		</part>
		<part>
			<title>Part 2</title>
			<exercices>
				<ex>
					<text>wee weed wed were wet sweet sweeter wee weed wed were wet sweet sweeter</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>weeds weeded seed seeds seeded weeds weeded seed seeds seeded</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>lool look loot hoot tool fool fools lool look loot hoot tool fool fools</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>dull duller full fuller hull hulls hullo dull duller full fuller hull hulls hullo</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>toll tolls roll rolls told fold folds toll tolls roll rolls told fold folds</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>juj jyyj joy toy roy try fry juj jyyj joy toy roy try fry juj jyyj joy toy roy try fry</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>jit hit fit dit wit lit litter jit hit fit dit wit lit litter jit hit fit dit wit lit litter</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>wet wets jet jets let lets letters wet wets jet jets let lets letters</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>try fried food; jets fly high; wet litter; try to fly; try fried food; jets fly high; wet litter;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>folded rolls; fred looks duller; red toy kite; jittery jet; freds red roll looks duller;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>the first red kite flies higher; let the wet kite dry; weed seeds;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>little red dolls roll; toy dolls for wee jill; look for freddie;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>first flight for fred; jill jilted hugh west; first flight for fred; jill jilted hugh west;</text>
				</ex>
			</exercices>
		</part>
	</level>
	
	<level>
		<title>Level 3</title>
		<part>
			<exercices>
				<ex>
					<text>fvf frfvf fbf frfbf rev vet fvf frfvf fbf frfbf rev vet</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>five fiver fib fibber very every five fiver fib fibber very every</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>jmj jujmj jnj jujnj jmj jujmj jnj jujnj</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>jim him tim rim hem them jim him tim rim hem them</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>jnj jujnj tin fin din dint tint jnj jujnj tin fin din dint tint</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>ten tent often den dent over oven ten tent often den dent over oven</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>men mend mended mine mind moment remember mend mended mine mind</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>ou ough rough tough trough enough ou ough rough tough trough enough</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>though thought through thorough though thought through thorough</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>house houses mouse mound mounds house houses mouse mound mounds</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>round rounds sound resounded round rounds sound resounded</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>ion lion mention vision visions ion lion mention vision visions</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>iou ious conscious envious mission missions iou ious conscious envious missions</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>john mentioned the lions and tigers; they looked very tough;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>the little mouse went round the house which stood on a high mound;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>i remember the mission which is built on the high ground beyond the valley;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>i rested in my house before playing two rounds of golf;</text>
				</ex>
			</exercices>
		</part>
	</level>
	
	<level>
		<title>Level 4</title>
		<part>
			<exercices>
				<ex>
					<text>ded dcd dedcd decided deck decked check cheese chest</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>cheek creek creeks dice slice sliced twice</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>type slowly with correct fingers; check the colours in the finger columns;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>notice which finger should type the letter key you need;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>when you come to tricky words type them more times;</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>The full stop is on the bottom row; use the ring finger.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>The comma is to the left of the full stop; use your longest finger.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>To start a new line, press the Enter key once.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Hold the Right Shift key for these left hand capitals.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Try to keep your fingers curved.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Do not let your wrists rest on the desk. That wastes energy.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>The trees were very, very wet. We will get wet when we go outside.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Do not type for too long without stretching your shoulders, neck, wrists, fingers.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Keep your legs uncrossed. Keep your feet on the floor.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>It helps if you remember which finger types which key.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Look before you cross the street or you might get knocked down.</text>
				</ex>
				<ex>
					<text>Jimmy took Henry to town to buy something. He bought four good story books.</text>
				</ex>
			</exercices>
		</part>
	</level>
</levels>